const DummyResult = [
  {
    id: 1,
    category_id: 1,
    category_title: 'Basic 500',
    words: [
      {
        word_id: 1,
        question: 'Test Onlu',
        answer: '23',
        correct_answer: ' 1',
      },
      {
        word_id: 2,
        question: 'Fly',
        answer: 'Test 1',
        correct_answer: 'Testing',
      },
      {
        word_id: 3,
        question: '走る',
        answer: 'Run',
        correct_answer: 'Testing Basinc',
      },
      {
        word_id: 4,
        question: '歩く',
        answer: 'Walk',
        correct_answer: 'Walk',
      },
      {
        word_id: 5,
        question: ' 友人',
        answer: 'i',
        correct_answer: 'Friend',
      },
      {
        word_id: 6,
        question: 'Run',
        answer: 'Testing ',
        correct_answer: 'Testinasg Basinc',
      },
      {
        word_id: 7,
        question: 'Run',
        answer: 'Last',
        correct_answer: 'Testinasg Basinc',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    category_id: 2,
    category_title: 'Basic Testaaing',
    words: [
      {
        word_id: 8,
        question: 'This is Correct sa',
        answer: 'Test 1',
        correct_answer: 'Test 1',
      },
      {
        word_id: 9,
        question: 'Fly',
        answer: 'Test 1',
        correct_answer: 'Testing',
      },
      {
        word_id: 10,
        question: '走る',
        answer: 'Run',
        correct_answer: 'Testing Basinc',
      },
      {
        word_id: 11,
        question: '歩く',
        answer: 'Walk',
        correct_answer: 'Walk',
      },
      {
        word_id: 12,
        question: ' 友人',
        answer: 'Friend',
        correct_answer: 'Friend',
      },
      {
        word_id: 13,
        question: 'Run',
        answer: 'Testing Mark',
        correct_answer: 'Testinasg Mark',
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default DummyResult;
